# 760-722-7131 104 Mayfair Street, Oceanside, CA 92058

#### Objective

To obtain employment in the field of computer science with an emphasis in design.

#### **Professional Profile**

Computer science student at UCSD with experience in Java, C, C++, Python, CSS, HTML, and Ocaml.

Bilingual and highly motivated individual with exceptional customer service skills, telephone reception skills, team-oriented mentality that arrives at any location with a positive attitude. He has several references that further emphasize his ability to work well with others.

Maintains a high level of productivity and focused on completing tasks in a timely fashion and giving proper attention to the job at hand. Well versed in computers, can communicate effectively with both customers and coworkers, and is willing to learn any and all necessary skills needed for this particular job. Has Previous experience in sales, and hopes to acquire more experience to further enhance his career.

### **Relevant skills:**

Microsoft Office Skills
Undergraduate at UCSD
Strong communication skills
Ability to develop strong client and employee relationships
Strong time management and organizational skills
Analytical/ Research Skills
Flexibility/Adaptability/Managing Multiple Priorities
Able to clarify the nature of a problem
Propose viable solutions
Able to build a relationship of mutual trust with clients
Able to handle complaints and concerns in a sensitive way
Typing speed of 50+ wpm
Marketing/Sales Experience
Responsive to client's needs and requests -- building customer rapport

Bilingual
Excellent Customer service skills
Multi-Tasking

Professionalism

Teamwork

Positive Attitude

Ability to communicate effectively with clients and co-workers

Accuracy and attention to detail

Tolerant and flexible to different situations

**Organization and Prioritization Skills** 

Willing to Learn

Motivated Individual

Hard Worker

**Public Speaking Skills** 

Investigates all possible solutions to a problem

Able to use a variety of software programs

Able to design and maintain filing and control systems

Capacity to adapt to new situations and settings and to tolerate well to change

## **Work History**

EVS (Environmental Specialist Lead) Kaiser Permanente 09/2013- 04/2016 ABM Janitorial Services – San Diego, CA

- Responsible for performing overall cleaning and maintenance of Kaiser Permanente Medical Center.
- Oversee the porters and janitorial staff to ensure is done properly and meet with the occasional client about services provided
- Responding to client requests and inquiries regarding current and potential new services
- Monitor building security and safety by performing such tasks as locking doors after operating hours
- Cleaning windowsills and windows
- Empty waste baskets and replace liners
- Dust/clean tops of office furniture
- Wipe/clean all table tops and chairs
- Vacuum all carpeting
- Clean glass on lobby door
- Clean sink and counter areas
- Clean building floors by sweeping, mopping, scrubbing, coating with sealer/finish and burnishing
- Clean, sanitize, and restock supplies in bathrooms, guestrooms, and common areas
- Maintain janitorial closets and equipment in a clean, safe, and operable condition
- Replacing all Red Sharp containers when full and recycling of used medical needles

## Maintenance Worker, 02/2011- Present

- Professional Maintenance Systems San Diego, CA
   Generally I was responsible for performing overall cleaning and maintenance of assigned area inside a specific building. Exact tasks are not definite, for that reason, I am flexible in performing assigned duties. Basic Responsibilities
- Cleaning windowsills and windows
- Clean building floors by sweeping, mopping, scrubbing, coating with sealer/finish and burnishing
- Clean, sanitize, and restock supplies in bathrooms, guestrooms, and common areas
- Empty all trash cans and replace liners, clean receptacles as necessary
- Maintain janitorial closets and equipment in a clean, safe, and operable condition
- Monitor building security and safety by performing such tasks as locking doors after operating hours and setting alarms

#### Education

High School Diploma: 2012 Oceanside High School

Oceanside , CA

Current computer science student 2012-Present

University of California, San Diego

La Jolla, CA

The Regional Occupational Program (ROP) certificate in Photoshop

### References

Susan Sim ABM Facility Services Supervisor and Kaiser Permanente EVS Supervisor San Diego CA, 92123 (619)-204-0103

Sarah Schoenleber College Program Coordinator Simon Family Foundation 901 Calle Amanecer, Suite #150 San Clemente, CA 92673

Office: 949.373.3500